ARCHIE BATTLEY

DETAILS

EMAIL

archie@archiebattley.com

MY WEBSITE archiebattley.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/archie-battley-7bb058221

SKILLS

Customer Relations

Graphic Design

Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Illustrator, Lightroom, Substance 3D Painter

Blender, Maya, Quixel Bridge

HOBBIES

Lakeside fishing, Swimming & Diving, Motorsports, Photography and Filming, Movies, Music, Computing, Video Games

PROFILE

I am currently a student at UAL studying 3D Computer Animation BA (Hons) I have Over 5 years experience in web design, video production and marketing for clients in the automotive industry. Strong computer literacy, high proficiency in many creative workflows, strong in customer relations and patron-focused.

8+ years experience of using Adobe Creative Suite applications. During my degree I am currently studying using a range of 3D production software: Maya, Blender, Substance 3D Painter, ZBrush, Marvelous Designer, Unreal Engine and Quixel Bridge

I am extremely interested in 3D computer graphics and all of the applications in which this industry extends. However I am very passionate about movies and games and would love to work for a studio.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Calibration Service Technician

Bramley, Surrey Jun 2022 — Sep 2022

I worked as a service technician for Gedore Torque Ltd. Repairing and calibrating torque measurement tools used in engineering, aerospace and medical applications. Clients I completed calibrations for included: Ford UK, MBDA, and Rolls Royce. I learned quickly how to complete calibrations to the UKAS accreditation standard that many of these companies request.

Web Design & Video Production Assistant, Racecar New Media Services

Shere, Surrey Jun 2015 — Sep 2020

After interning at Racecar during my work experience week at school I was brought on part time as a member of the team for a summer job. I subsequently returned every summer during my school days, eventually working there full time after completing my studies at sixth form during my gap years. I was naturally proficient at website graphics and video production so most of my duties involved filming and editing simple videos for various clients in the automotive and motorsports industry as well as supplanting their brand identity and improving their web page design. I have also created ads for car magazines and photographed classifieds for classic car dealers.

I thoroughly enjoyed my work there and I feel it has supplemented my communication and interpersonal skills and challenged me to think creatively. I enjoyed the increasing value that I felt I added to the team with my contributions as I progressed and gained valuable experience. It also inspired me to pursue a career in the creative industry as my skills and interest in creative applications developed.

EDUCATION

Batchelor of Arts in 3D Computer Animation, University of the Arts London, London College of Communication

London

Expected 2:1 June 2023

C in Graphic Design, Godalming College

Godalming

Sep 2016 - Jun 2018

Godalming

C in Geography, Godalming College

Sep 2016 - Jun 2018

Merit in IT, Godalming College

Sep 2016 - Jun 2018

Godalming